<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QuotesApp</string>
    <!-- making array for storing Quotes -->
    <string-array name="popularQuote">
        <item>When you grow up you tend to get told that the world is the way it is and
            your life is just to live your life inside the world. Try not to bash into the walls
            too much. Try to have a nice family life, have fun, save a little money.
            That’s a very limited life. Life can be much broader once you discover one simple fact:
            Everything around you that you call life was made up by people that were no smarter than
            you. And you can change it, you can influence it… Once you learn that, you\'ll never
            be the same again.
            ― Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>Thinking is progress. Non-thinking is stagnation of the individual, organization and
            the country. Thinking leads to action. Knowledge without action is useless and
            irrelevant. Knowledge with action converts adversity into prosperity.
            — Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam</item>
        <item>It is impossible to live without failing at something, unless you live so cautiously
            that you might as well not have lived at all, in which case you have failed by default.
            — J. K. Rowling</item>
        <item>I do think it’s important to follow your dreams and do something which you are
            excited by. If you follow your heart and do what you like, you will always do much
            better. It doesn\'t matter what your educational qualification is.
            — Sundar Pichai</item>
        <item> Indeed, that is My Path – perfectly straight. So follow it and do not follow other
            ways, for they will lead you away from His Way. This is what He has commanded you,
            so perhaps you will be conscious of Allah (God).
            Quran 6:153</item>
        <item>You can search throughout the entire universe for someone who is more deserving of
            your love and affection than you are yourself, and that person is not to be found
            anywhere. You yourself, as much as anybody in the entire universe deserve your love and
            affection.
            — Buddha</item>
        <item>You are the last thought in my mind before I drift off to sleep and the first thought
            when I wake up each morning.
            – Unknown</item>
        <item>— Dont care or cry for someone who doesn\'t give a shit about what you feel. You are
            losing out the bright side if you are doing so. Guys/girls will come and go out of your
            life; however, the right one will arrive at the right time for you. Till then, keep calm
            and enjoy life.</item>
        <item>You Will Never Live A Perfect Life – Getting In A Relationship Is Like Diving
            In A Sea, You Can Drown And Whales And Sharks Can Kill You. On The Other Hand,
            Being Single Is Like Staying Away From That Water, You Will Starve.</item>
        <item>— Be a real person with a unique attitude. Even if someone doesn\'t like your attitude,
            don’t apologize for it. You are doing what you think is right, and
            there is no point in apologizing.</item>
        <item>Your work is going to fill a large part of your life, and the only way to be truly
            satisfied is to do what you believe is great work. And the only way to do great work is
            to love what you do. If you haven\'t found it yet, keep looking. Dont settle.
            As with all matters of the heart, youll know when you find it.
            ― Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>Sometimes when you innovate, you make mistakes. It is best to admit them quickly, and
            get on with improving your other innovations.
            ― Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>Design is a funny word. Some people think design means how it looks. But of course,
            if you dig deeper, its really how it works.
             ― Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>To turn really interesting ideas and fledgling technologies into a company that can
            continue to innovate for years, it requires a lot of disciplines.
            ― Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>Remembering that Ill be dead soon is the most important tool Ive ever encountered to
            help me make the big choices in life. Because almost everything - all external
            expectations, all pride, all fear of embarrassment or failure - these things just fall
            away in the face of death, leaving only what is truly important.
            ― Steve Jobs</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
